forex-metal.com 2015-03-16

# Forex Trading | CFD Trading | Trading on the Forex | Currency Trading | Forex News | Forex-Metal

By accepting our Terms of Service and the Privacy Policy at the time when you apply for an account with us you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. 

When you ask for information about our products and services, when you access and use this website or when you submit an application to open an account with Forex-Metal.com, you will be providing Forex-Metal.com with your personal information. We will also maintain records of all transactions and activities on accounts you have with Forex-Metal.com, including details of contracts traded and margin calls made. During the course of your relationship with Forex-Metal.com, we will also gather information about products and services provided to you. 

When assessing your application, Forex-Metal.com may also collect information about you from publicly available sources such as company registers. A customer is entitled to gain access to the information that the Forex-Metal.com holds about him or her in accordance with this privacy policy. 

The Forex-Metal.com reserves the right to record telephone conversations between you and persons working for the Forex-Metal.com. Such recordings, or transcripts from such recordings, may be used to resolve any dispute between you and Forex-Metal.com. 

The Forex-Metal.com will also collect and hold information about you when you complete an online application or other type of form or access and trade your account through our website. We also collect all kinds of statistical information about visitors to our websites. This information is used to evaluate and improve the performance of our website. Other than statistical information, we do not collect any information about you through our website unless you provide the information to us. 

We do not collect or store any credit card/debit card details of our customers. 

You should also be aware that we use cookies on our websites. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes a unique identification number or value that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookies to your browser if your browser allows it. 

When you access your account on-line a cookie will be created which uniquely identifies your computer and your username and password. This means that you do not have to re-enter those details each time you want to access your account on-line. 

Most internet browsers are set up to accept cookies. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may be able to change the settings of your browser to refuse all cookies or to have your computer notify you each time a cookie is sent to it, and thereby give yourself the choice whether to accept it or not. If you reject all cookies, you will be unable to access your account on-line. You can also delete cookies from your computer after they have been created. 

The information requested in any application to open an account completed by customers is required to enable us to determine your trading needs and experience in order to provide you with better service. That information, together with the information collected and maintained by the Forex-Metal.com during the course of our relationship with you, is required to keep you updated whilst you are a Customer in relation to matters such as Contracts you have traded, your margin obligations and the funds in your account, and possibly other activities of the Forex-Metal.com. Forex-Metal.com also requires the information to manage and administer the products and services provided to you. 

The information requested by us when you are accessing Forex-Metal.com websites is to allow us to provide you with information regarding the products and services offered by Forex-Metal.com. We may also be required to provide your personal information regulatory and government bodies in our jurisdiction. 

The Forex-Metal.com may also disclose your personal information to: 

  * financial institutions and other similar organizations that it deals with in the course of its corporate activities, or those that are nominated by you; 
  * any organization at your request or any persons acting on your behalf, including your financial adviser, broker, solicitor or accountant. 

The Forex-Metal.com may use your personal information for: 

  * contacting you in regards to our new products and services; 
  * developing an understanding of the products and services that you may be interested in obtaining from the Forex-Metal.com. 

We take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information from misuse, loss, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure. Under no circumstances will your personal details be sold or given to other party, apart from cases indicated above. In some circumstances the law may allow us to deny you access to your personal information held by us. In such a case we will explain to you the reason for refusing access. You may ask us at any time to correct personal information held by Forex-Metal.com about you, and which you believe is inaccurate. By accessing this website you consent to the Forex-Metal.com collecting, maintaining, using and disclosing personal information about you and provided by you or by another person as described above. This Privacy Policy came into effect in December 2007 and was last updated on 23rd April 2014.
